http://www.laser.com/info.php/information/Privacy_Notice/page/privacy/osCsid/ssk5m11jcihe1tuor7lugv9hn5

Cart ContentsCheckoutMy Account
Top » Catalogue » Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
We are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our pledge is to safeguard any personal information that you provide us, and to make every reasonable effort to use this information only as you choose.
Laser Business Systems Ltd. complies with the principles of the UK Data Protection Act 2018 when dealing with all data received from visitors to the web site. All orders and payment processing are handled by Laser Business Systems Limited.
Data is only used for the purposes described in our entry on the UK Data Protection Register, registration number Z640518X.
The type of information we will collect about you includes:
Your name
Address
Telephone number
E-mail address
Credit/debit card details
We only hold personal data for as long as necessary to offer services provided on the web site. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. Once data is no longer needed it is deleted from our files and from our server. Customers can check the information we hold by sending an e-mail to us with adequate proof of identity.
Should you find any inaccuracies, we will delete or correct it promptly. We do not give, rent or sell mailing lists to third parties.
If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area), we will always obtain your consent first.
We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our website. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually configure your browser to prevent this from happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you from subsequent visits to our website unless you modify your browser settings.
While we strive to protect your personal information, you should also take steps to protect your information. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information while you are on the Internet. At a minimum, we encourage you to change your passwords often, using a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure that you are using a secure browser as you surf the Internet.
Contact Us
If you have questions or concerns about your privacy when using our website, please contact us at:
Laser Business Systems Ltd.
16 Garthland Drive
Barnet
Hertfordshire EN5 3BB
UK
Telephone:
020 8441 9788 (UK)+44 20 8441 9788 (International)
Fax:
020 8449 0430 (UK)+44 20 8449 0430 (International)
Office Hours: Monday to Friday, 09:00 to 17:00 local time.
Continue
laser.com | cbus-shop.comCopyright © 2020 Laser Business Systems Ltd.
Categories C-Bus Lighting Control-> (330)KNX Building Automation-> (6)Comfort Security/Home Automation-> (146)Barix Audio Streaming-> (34)X-10 Home Automation-> (21)Saturn 250V (2)Modular Enclosures-> (32)Power & Protection (15)E Series (25)Ethernet Devices (1)Backboxes (6)Cable (5)
Manufacturers Please SelectBarixClipsalCytechDomiaFarfisa IntercomsGenericLantronixLEBMarmitekMerlin GerinSarelSchneider ElectricX10Xantech
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for. Advanced Search
What's New? LSS5500SHAC - C-Bus Wiser for C-Bus Automation Controller£885.00 (£1,062.00 inc VAT)
Information
About Us Contact Information Delivery and Returns Integrators/Partners/Installers Links and Documentation Privacy Notice Terms and Conditions
We Accept
Shopping Cart 0 items
C-Bus
Bestsellers 157/1 - C-Bus Flush Mounting J Back Box 94Hx54Wx43D5005C305B-1M - C-Bus Pink Cable CAT5e (by the metre)CABRJ45/8WCC - RJ45 Plug - For Solid CableS31LCDA - Load Correction Device5753L - Indoor PIR Movement Sensor, 360 degreeL5508D1A - C-Bus Dimmer, 8 channel, 220V AC, 1A, with power supply5085DLGF - C-Bus Saturn 5 Gang DLT Key Input White (Ocean Mist)157/1P - C-Bus Flush mounting J back box Plastic 94Hx54Wx43D9WE - E-Series Plain Screw Caps White5082NLGF - C-Bus Saturn Input Switch 2 Gang Rectangular White
